(Leonard:)You're still awake?
(Sheldon:)For a man whose
last observation was
(Sheldon:)our universe may be the surface
(Sheldon:)of a multidimensional
supercooled liquid,
"you're still awake" seems
like quite the sophomore slump.
(Leonard:)You worked out
all the math.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I did more
than work out all the math.
(Sheldon:)I wrote a paper.
(Leonard:)You wrote a paper
on my idea?
(Sheldon:)I wrote a paper
on our idea.
(Leonard:)When did my idea
become our idea?
(Sheldon:)When I mixed it with
Sheldony goodness
(Sheldon:)and cooked it in the
Easy-Bake Oven of my mind.
(Leonard:)This is good.
(Leonard:)Our idea is really good.
(Sheldon:)Well, the lightbulb in this
oven is ridiculously bright.
(Leonard:)You know, if no one's
thought of this, yet,
(Leonard:)this could be a big deal.
(Sheldon:)Only way we'll
know for sure is
(Sheldon:)if we post it online to
the pre-print server.
(Sheldon:)I have it ready to go, but I
wasn't gonna do it without you.